naturalblaze.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Natural Blaze

Naturalblaze.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Naturalblaze.com currently collects no personal information about who visits our site. Naturalblaze.com uses a hit service that shows information such as which internet service visitors are using, their screen resolutions, browser types, etc… but in no way does this reveal the name, email address, or any specific information whatsoever about the site’s visitors.

#### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

The Site uses DoubleClick, a third party advertising provider, to serve advertisements on the Site. Advertising providers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to the Site and other web sites you have visited, allowing targeted advertisements to be delivered to you for products and services in which you might be interested. Third party advertising providers, advertisers (whose ads are displayed via the advertising provider) may use cookies, web beacons, embedded scripts or other similar mechanisms to automatically collect web site usage information. Third party advertising providers and the advertisers may use this web site usage information for, among other purposes, helping deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in, to prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times, and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements are to you. Cookies, web beacons and embedded scripts and other similar mechanisms used to collect web site usage information from advertising providers, advertisers and traffic measurement services are governed by their respective privacy policies and not this Privacy Policy.

However, we do not share any Personal Information with these third parties in connection with their performing these services on the Web Site.  
For more information about DoubleClick, including instructions on how to opt out of DoubleClick’s targeted advertising, please see [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx). For additional information about how to opt out of targeted advertising from DoubleClick and other members of the Network Advertising Initiative, please see [http://www.networkadvertising.org/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

#### Will Naturalblaze.com disclose collected information to outside parties?

Naturalblaze.com may eventually disclose the aforementioned GENERAL information about visitors – information that does NOT identify who you are. We may disclose answers to questions such as: during what time periods do we receive the most visitors, what is the most common browser version of our visitors, what are the most popular internet services our visitors use, etc. We will never release contact details of any registered users of our website. The last thing we want is “spam” reaching our visitors.

#### Your Consent:

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Naturalblaze.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. But, now and forever we put your privacy first before any other concerns. We will never sell lists of email addresses from this site. We respect the privacy of our visitors.

#### Affiliate Disclosure:

Naturalblaze.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

#### Newsletter:

Visitors on this site may optionally sign up for our daily newsletter by providing their email address in one of the various signup forms available on naturalblaze.com. The email addresses are stored with mailchimp.com, and the user data is never shared nor sold to any outside parties. The Mailchimp privacy policy an be seen here <https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/>. We use the subscribers email address to send out a daily newsletter with the most recent articles, and to communicate with regarding changes or updates on the site. In addition we also send out occasional promotional emails to our subscribers, for products that we think would be of interest. Users emails are kept safe by Mailchimp, for as long as the user remains a subscriber. Users can unsubscribe from our email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the base of the email.
